A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Secretary of Finance, 1992; 1994; 2000-2018 (bulk 2013-2017)
Library of Virginia
- Series VII. Special Projects and Studies, 2012; 2014; 2016-2017., Extent: 2 boxes (1.35 cu. ft.). (Box 26-27)
  - Petersburg, 2016 July-Aug. (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Petersburg, 2016 Aug. (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Petersburg, 2016 Aug-Sept. (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Petersburg, 2016 Aug. (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Petersburg, 2016 Aug. (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Petersburg, 2016 Sept. (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Petersburg, 2016 Sept. (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Petersburg, 2016 Sept. (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Petersburg, 2016 Sept-Oct. (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Petersburg, 2016 Oct-Nov. (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Petersburg, 2017 Feb-Apr. (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Petersburg, 2017 Jan. (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Petersburg, 2017 Jan. (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Petersburg, 2016 Dec-2017 Jan. (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Petersburg (Reference Materials), 2016 Feb-Mar. (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Petersburg (Reference Materials), 2012 July-Aug. (Box 27, Folder 16)